# Francisco Moreno

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

LinkedIn in

<u>GitHub</u>

(+34) 678 127 297



fran.moreno.se@gmail.com



Castellón de la Plana, Castellón, Spain



## **ABOUT ME**

Proven Junior Software Engineer with 1+ years of experience in Machine Learning applied to Computer Vision and 1 year of experience in Software Test Automation. As a dedicated problem solver, I display a seasoned experience in Python and libraries/frameworks to solve real-world problems through code. In the course of my last job, I have gained hands-on experience in industry-standard development, as well as develop great analytical skills. Currently, my goal is to keep growing as an interdisciplinary software engineer to master my skills and acquire new ones.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Universitat Jaume I

M.Sc. in Intelligent Systems 2020 - 2021

#### University of Málaga

B.S. in Electronics, Robotics and Mechatronics 2016 - 2020

#### **SKILLS**

- Python
- MySQL
- PyTorch, Tensorflow, Keras
- Unix, Bash
- Git
- Azure DevOps (Pipelines)
- AWS (EC2, S3, EBS)
- Docker, Kubernetes
- HTML, CSS, Javascript
- C, C++
- NoSQL (Cassandra, MongoDB, Neo4j)

#### **COURSES**

- Expertise in Big Data (4 months)
- Software Designer Mindset (4 months)
- Introduction to NLP

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

- IbPRIA 2022
- OCEANS 2021

## **SPOKEN LANGUAGES**

- Spanish (Native)
- English (Professional level)

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **Test Automation Engineer**

BDR Thermea Group | Apr. 2022 - Feb. 2023

- Defining integration, performance and regression test plans to define the development state of a generic appliance of the company. Tests implemented with Robot Framework.
- Creating functional pipelines in Azure DevOps with proven benefits in CI/CD procedures against the previous approach with Jenkins.
- Continuous involvement to improve the team's accomplishment and results with Agile methodologies.

#### **Junior Machine Learning Engineer**

Fisabio Foundation | Sept. 2021 - Mar. 2022

- Results of 95% hit while classifying malfunctioning glomeruli
  in renal tissue images after applying an image segmentation
  network based on U-net architecture. Developed, trained and
  tested from scratch with Keras.
- Optimization of time costs by pre-processing original images with MATLAB and Python to obtain sub-images that can be fed to the model, so the result can be represented in its original format.
- Obtained experience while operating with a Linux cluster during the network training process.

#### **Research Technical Support**

Universitat Jaume I | Feb. 2021 - Jul. 2021

- Cooperated in the Spanish national project <u>ReAVIPeRo</u>
   developing a hybrid CNN-LSTM Neural Network model
   architecture from scratch with PyTorch. Design, train and
   validation were performed. Work added to my Master's Thesis,
   obtaining excellent final results.
- Published a scientific paper in <u>IbPRIA22</u> Conference about the research in the usage of Event-based images for First-person human action recognition with outstanding results compared to conventional cameras.